{
  "apple": [
    {
      "question": "As per the article read, where is Apple planning on making iPhones in India?",
      "options": [
        "New Delhi",
        "Hyderabad",
        "Bangalore",
        "Mumbai"
      ],
      "correct": "Bangalore"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article read, which of the following companies would be a collaborator in Apple's new factories in India?",
      "options": [
        "Toshiba",
        "Jabil",
        "Foxconn",
        "Wistron"
      ],
      "correct": "Wistron"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to the article, what percentage of raw material must be locally sourced, as mandated by Indian laws?",
      "options": [
        "40%",
        "50%",
        "30%",
        "20%"
      ],
      "correct": "30%"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, India is projected to overtake which country as the world's second largest smartphone market?",
      "options": [
        "U.S.A.",
        "China",
        "Europe",
        "Brazil"
      ],
      "correct": "U.S.A."
    }
  ],
  "volcano": [
    {
      "question": "As per the article read, in which of the following years did the Barren Island Volcano see a major eruption?",
      "options": [
        "2005",
        "2009",
        "1944",
        "1991"
      ],
      "correct": "1991"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, scientists from which Indian agency/institute were observing the volcano?",
      "options": [
        "Indian Meteorological Department",
        "National Institute of Oceanography",
        "I.I.T., Madras",
        "National Institute of Earthquake Engineering"
      ],
      "correct": "National Institute of Oceanography"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the article on India's active volcano, which Indian scientist was quoted?",
      "options": [
        "Dr. Abhay Madhulkar",
        "Dr. Madhur Garg",
        "Dr. Venkat Gopal",
        "Dr. Abhyanand Krishna"
      ],
      "correct": "Dr. Abhay Madhulkar"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, where is the volcano located?",
      "options": [
        "Lakshadweep",
        "Daman & Diu",
        "Wheeler Island",
        "Andaman & Nicobar Islands"
      ],
      "correct": "Andaman & Nicobar Islands"
    }
  ],
  "law": [
    {
      "question": "As per the article, Yogendra Vasupal and Sachit Singhi  are the founder of which company?",
      "options": [
        "Zostel",
        "Trivago",
        "Stayzilla",
        "OYO Rooms"
      ],
      "correct": "Stayzilla"
    },
    {
      "question": "When was Fabmall.com founded by K Vaitheeswaran?",
      "options": [
        "1995",
        "1999",
        "2005",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correct": "1999"
    },
    {
      "question": "In November 2015, Gaurav Chaudhary, the co-founder of which startup was kept hostage for over two days sacked employees?",
      "options": [
        "TinyOwl",
        "Sabzi.com",
        "Stayzilla",
        "Fruitly"
      ],
      "correct": "TinyOwl"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, this Bengaluru-based logistics startup office was vandalised by its delivery boys after non-payment of salaries for months. Which startup is it?",
      "options": [
        "Sabzi.com",
        "Townrush",
        "Deliveroo",
        "Fruitly"
      ],
      "correct": "Townrush"
    }
  ],
  "justice": [
    {
      "question": "As per teh article, which terror outfit were primary accused of the Hyderabad blast associated with?",
      "options": [
        "Indian Mujahideen",
        "Lashkar-e-Taiba",
        "ISIS",
        "Al-Qaeda"
      ],
      "correct": "Indian Mujahideen"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, how many people were killed in the 2013 Hyderabad Blast?",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "18",
        "35",
        "58"
      ],
      "correct": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, who was the absconding primary accused in the Hyderabad blast case?",
      "options": [
        "Mohamed Rafeeq",
        "Aneeq Shafique Sayeed",
        "Yasin Bhatkal",
        "Riyaz Bhatkal"
      ],
      "correct": "Riyaz Bhatkal"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, which vehicle was used to mount the bombs?",
      "options": [
        "Bicycles",
        "Omni-van",
        "Mini Truck",
        "Auto-rickshaws"
      ],
      "correct": "Bicycles"
    }
  ],
  "train": [
    {
      "question": "As per the article, how many views did the video of the woman escaping an approaching train have?",
      "options": [
        "over 10 million",
        "over 1 million",
        "over 500,000",
        "over 5 million"
      ],
      "correct": "over 5 million"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, where was the video shared?",
      "options": [
        "YouTube",
        "circulated on WhatsApp",
        "Twitter",
        "Facebook"
      ],
      "correct": "YouTube"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, what was the explanation suggested for how the woman ended up on the tracks?",
      "options": [
        "she fell while crossing them",
        "she got stuck while picking up her fallen luggage",
        "she slipped and fell from the platform",
        "she was accidentally pushed by people rushing to get on the train"
      ],
      "correct": "she fell while crossing them"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the article, which of the following adjectives were used in the article to describe the woman?",
      "options": [
        "Mischievous",
        "Intelligent",
        "Foolhardy",
        "Brave"
      ],
      "correct": "Brave"
    }
  ],
  "delhi": [
    {
      "question": "According to the article, what is the term used to refer to the newly appointed workers against open defecation?",
      "options": [
        "Swachh Sewak",
        "Dilli Sewak",
        "Swachh Karmachari",
        "Dilli Karmachari"
      ],
      "correct": "Swachh Sewak"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to the article, how would the new appointees ensure a defecation free Delhi?",
      "options": [
        "they will escort the offenders to the nearest police station",
        "they will collect a fine of Rs.1,000 from offenders",
        "they will publicly name and shame the offenders",
        "they will blow a whistle and direct them to the nearest public toilet"
      ],
      "correct": "they will blow a whistle and direct them to the nearest public toilet"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the deadline set by India's PM for eradication of open-defecation?",
      "options": [
        "October, 2019",
        "January, 2020",
        "December, 2019",
        "June, 2019"
      ],
      "correct": "October, 2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "As per the article, open defecation leads to high rates of deaths in children under 5, from which of the following complications?",
      "options": [
        "Diarrhoea",
        "Influenza",
        "Tuberculosis",
        "Chikungunya"
      ],
      "correct": "Diarrhoea"
    }
  ]
}